Felix Hanley

Contact

PO Box 364

Kew East

VIC 3102

0466 823 984

felix@seconddrawer.com.au

http://seconddrawer.com.au

Summary

I am an Australian developer currently available for development and system administration positions. Having had experience in a variety of organisations I enjoy working in both small and large teams, particularly with new technologies.

Born in 1975 and married since 1997, I have a son born in 2008.

Education

Bachelor of Applied Science and Technology (deferred), Swinburne University, 1994 – 1995 Bachelor of Computer Science and Technology, The University of Sydney, 1999 – 2001

Skills

Languages & Software: Ruby, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Git, MySQL, PHP, AJAX, Magento, Languages & Software: Ruby, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Git, MySQL, PHP, AJAX, Magento, Languages & Software: Ruby, Photoshop/Gimp, Illustrator/Inkscape, Visual Basic, C/C++, Python, Perforce, Subversion

Frameworks: Ruby on Rails, Merb, Sinatra, jQuery, CakePHP **Other:** Reasonably fluent in Thai, working knowledge of Lahu

Experience

Second Drawer

Sydney/Melbourne/Thailand

2006 - Present

Experience in all aspects of web development for both public and private applications

- Web application development using Ruby, Javascript & PHP
 - · Code security auditing and performance optmisations in PHP, Ruby and SQL
 - Systems administration of Linux servers

Sensory Networks

Sydney

Web Application Developer

Freelance Consultant/Developer

2005 - 2006

Experience building and documenting highly customised applications under strict security and performance requirements

- Web application development for internal warehouse, CRM and CMS software used in 4 continents
- Documentation writing and formatting in XML/XSLT
- Auditing of code in various languages and continual security testing and auditing of externally facing interfaces and data.

Second Drawer

Sydney/Western Australia

Analyst/Programmer

1998 - 2004

Freelance consulting for many varied private companies, schools and mining & engineering firms in rural Australia

- · Linux systems & network administration
- Security audits on proprietary code and firewalls.
- Custom development of in-house applications as well as extensions and optmisation of existing applications
- Large scale mail, LDAP, web and backup server installations

National Telecoms Group

Sydney

Developer

DefineIT

2001 - 2002

A member of a small team of application developers working on Australia's largest distributed CRM

- The design, development, testing and continual maintenance of a Saleslogix CRM (in Visual Basic)
- Administration of 300+ seat Citrix installation
- Design and implementation of a large MSSQL cluster

Developer/Administrator

Sydney 1999 – 2001

- Programming and design for medical diagnosis web site.
- Administration of Linux, Solaris and Windows networks and services